<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="movies.xsl"?>
<!--<movies xmlns="http://www.w3schools.com/WSDassignment"
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
    xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.w3schools.com/WSDassignment movies.xsd">-->
  <movies>
    <movie>
        <title>28 days later</title>
        <genre>Horror</genre>
        <releaseDate>2002</releaseDate>
        <price>19.96</price>
        <picture></picture>
        <description>The naive activists ignore the pleas of a scientist to keep the cages locked, with disastrous results. 
            Twenty-eight days later, our protagonist, Jim (Alex Palmer), wakes up from a coma, alone, in an abandoned hospital. 
            He begins to seek out anyone else to find London is deserted, apparently without a living soul.</description>
        <availableCopies>21</availableCopies>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <title>Alien vs Predator</title>
        <genre>Sci-Fi</genre>
        <releaseDate>2004</releaseDate>
        <price>10.00</price>
        <picture></picture>
        <description>Directed by Paul W.S. Anderson, Alien vs. Predator follows billionaire Charles Bishop Weyland (Lance Henriksen) 
            and his team of drillers, scientists, and archaeologists, to an obscure pyramid site in Antarctica. 
            Among the icy ruins, allegedly, lies the proof of an empire predating humankind.</description>
        <availableCopies>2</availableCopies>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <title>Anchorman</title>
        <genre>Comedy</genre>
        <releaseDate>2004</releaseDate>
        <price>11.50</price>
        <picture></picture>
        <description>Ron Burgundy is the top-rated anchorman in San Diego in the '70s. When feminism marches into the 
            newsroom in the form of ambitious newswoman Veronica Corningstone, Ron is willing to play along at first-as long as 
            Veronica stays in her place, covering cat fashion shows, cooking, and other "female" interests.</description>
        <availableCopies>6</availableCopies>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <title>Baby Driver</title>
        <genre>Action</genre>
        <releaseDate>2017</releaseDate>
        <price>22.99</price>
        <picture></picture>
        <description>Baby Driver is a 2017 crime film written and directed by Edgar Wright. The plot follows Baby (Ansel Elgort), 
            a music lover who is coerced to work as a getaway driver for kingpin Doc (Kevin Spacey).</description>
        <availableCopies>1</availableCopies>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <title>Back to the future</title>
        <genre>Sci-Fi</genre>
        <releaseDate>1985</releaseDate>
        <price>12.99</price>
        <picture></picture>
        <description>Marty accidentally activates the time machine, sending him back to 1955 where he accidentally gets in the way of 
            his teenage parents meeting. Marty must find a way to convince Doc that he is from the future, reunite his parents, 
            and ultimately get back to the future.</description>
        <availableCopies>0</availableCopies>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <title>Batman Begins</title>
        <genre>Sci-Fi</genre>
        <releaseDate>2005</releaseDate>
        <price>17.10</price>
        <picture></picture>
        <description>A young Bruce Wayne (Christian Bale) travels to the Far East, where he's trained in the martial arts by Henri Ducard (Liam Neeson),
            a member of the mysterious League of Shadows. When Ducard reveals the League's true purpose -- the complete destruction of Gotham City -- 
            Wayne returns to Gotham intent on cleaning up the city without resorting to murder. </description>
        <availableCopies>4</availableCopies>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <title>Beetlejuice </title>
        <genre>Sci-Fi</genre>
        <releaseDate>1988</releaseDate>
        <price>9.99</price>
        <picture></picture>
        <description>The plot revolves around a recently deceased young couple (Alec Baldwin and Geena Davis) who become 
            ghosts haunting their former home, and an obnoxious, devious ghost named Betelgeuse (pronounced "Beetlejuice", portrayed by Michael Keaton)</description>
        <availableCopies>6</availableCopies>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <title>Despicable Me</title>
        <genre>Family</genre>
        <releaseDate>2010</releaseDate>
        <price>9.00</price>
        <picture></picture>
        <description>It follows the story of Gru, a super-villain who adopts three girls from an orphanage; and Vector, a rival of Gru who steals the 
            Great Pyramid of Giza. When Gru learns of Vector's heist, he plans an even greater heist: to shrink and steal the Earth's moon.</description>
        <availableCopies>32</availableCopies>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <title>Die Hard</title>
        <genre>Action</genre>
        <releaseDate>1988</releaseDate>
        <price>4.99</price>
        <picture></picture>
        <description>John McClane, a detective with the New York City Police Department, arrives in Los Angeles to attempt a 
            Christmas reunion and reconciliation with his estranged wife Holly (Bonnie Bedelia), who is attending a party thrown by 
            her employer, the Nakatomi Corporation, at its still-unfinished American branch office</description>
        <availableCopies>4</availableCopies>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <title>Home alone</title>
        <genre>Family</genre>
        <releaseDate>1990</releaseDate>
        <price>7.99</price>
        <picture></picture>
        <description>The film stars Macaulay Culkin as Kevin McCallister, a boy who is mistakenly left behind when his family flies to Paris for 
            their Christmas vacation. Kevin initially relishes being home alone, but soon has to contend with two 
            burglars played by Joe Pesci and Daniel Stern.</description>
        <availableCopies>7</availableCopies>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <title>I Robot</title>
        <genre>Sci-Fi</genre>
        <releaseDate>2004</releaseDate>
        <price>11.49</price>
        <picture></picture>
        <description>Set in a future Earth (2035 A.D.) where robots are common assistants and workers for their human owners,
            this is the story of "robotophobic" Chicago Police Detective Del Spooner's investigation into the murder of Dr. Alfred Lanning, 
            who works at U.S. Robotics, in which a robot, Sonny , appears to be implicated</description>
        <availableCopies>8</availableCopies>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <title>Land of the Dead</title>
        <genre>Horror</genre>
        <releaseDate>2005</releaseDate>
        <price>3.99</price>
        <picture></picture>
        <description>In a world where zombies form the majority of the population, the remaining humans build a feudal 
            society away from the undead. Ruthless Paul Kaufman (Dennis Hopper) rules and protects this microcosm but enforces 
            painful class distinctions. Second-in-command Cholo DeMora (John Leguizamo) attempts to lead a secret rebellion against 
            Kaufman's tyranny</description>
        <availableCopies>1</availableCopies>
    </movie>
</movies>
